Guide to the Alpha Delta Phi records,1897-1988
Alpha Delta Phi records,1897-1988
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alpha Delta Phi records, 1897-1988.
37-4-2101
Alpha Delta Phi.Cornell Chapter.
5.1 cubic ft.
Computer Media, Correspondence, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Publications
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Alpha Delta Phi ephemera.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Secretary's minutes, 1897-1975; constitution and bylaws, with list of members, 1878-1926; correspondence and documents about the sale of property and the settlement of the Martin McVoy, Jr. estate, 1963-1988, and seal imprinter. Also includes "Catalogue of the Alpha Delta Phi, 1932-1956"; THE CAYUGAN, 1964, 1966; brochures containing messages from the faculty advisor and president, 1963-1966; initiation programs, 1964, 1965; membership roster, 1965; and photographs. Also the files of G. Lauriston Walsh as alumni association president regarding the operation and events of the fraternity.
Also, inscribed copy of Memorial of Samuel Eels, the founder of Alpha Delta Phi, 1873, and Alpha Delta Phi Song Book, 1912.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Alpha Delta Phi.; Cornell University--Societies, etc.
Titles:
Cayugan.
Subjects:
Greek letter societies.; Initiations (into trades, societies, etc.)
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the records requires written consent of the President of the Alumni Board of Directors or his designee. Library staff will first notify the President of any requests.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Series II. Printed Materials
Series III. Fraternal Documents
Series IV. G. Lauriston Walsh Files, President of Alpha Delta Phi Alumni Association
Series IV. Photographs and Negatives
Series IV. Other
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Letter, 1869 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Letter, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Letter from Edward E. Hole, Sept. 26, 1880 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Letter from chapter to W. H. Fox and C. E. Maniene, Nov. 16, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Letter from W. C. Bradley, May 11, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Letter from Prof. Tracy Peck regarding Walter R. Sherman, June 15, 1875 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Letter from Marcus Lyon, June 15, 1875 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Letter from graduate members expressing concern over refusal to vote a charter to proposed University of California chapter, April 1894 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Series II. Printed materials
  - Miscellaneous publications (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Catalogue of the Alpha Delta Phi 1832-1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Catalogue of the Alpha Delta Phi (2 copies), 1851 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Cornellian, 1878-1879 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Oration delivered before the Biennial Convention of the Alpha Delta Phi Society, Samuel Eells, 1839 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Convention addresses (also 1 floppy disk), 1889-1891 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University Record of the Class of 1877, 1873-1923 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - outlines on a course in history, Andrew D. White, 1872 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alpha Delta Phi twenty-fifth anniversary, 1858 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous printed items, 1840-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous printed materials and forms, 1908-1957 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous printed materials, 1901-1995 (Box 4)
- Series III. Fraternity Documents
  - Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity at Cornell University - Constitution and By Laws, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretary's minute book [Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity at Cornell University - Alumni Corporation Minutes], 1897-1940 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity at Cornell University - Alumni Corporation Minutes, 1940-1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Alpha Delta Phi Fraternity at Cornell University - Alumni Corporation Minutes, 1963-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Financial notes, correspondence, photocopy of agreement with Cornell University, 1954-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Legal documents, 1963-1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Adelphic Fund Drive, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - List of chapters and confidential prospectus (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - First Annual Report of Cornell Chapter, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    -Continuation on verso of item in Folder 28 of Box 8
  - List of men to whom invitations to annual reunion were sent, 1879 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Report of the delegates to the 45th convention of the Cornell chapter, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Incorporation of Alpha Delta Phi at Cornell, 1878 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Subscriptions to the house fund and hall chandelier (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - List of names, 1946-1949, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Roll call, 1906-2003 (Box 10)
  - Meeting minutes, ca. 1917-1955 (Box 10)
  - Visitor’s Book, 1894-2002 (Box 11)
  - Board of Directors meeting minutes, 1996, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Contact sheets, general info, traditions and history, international policy, ca. 1970-1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Brothers Book, 2001, 2004, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Pledge and Brothers list, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Memorial of Samuel Eells, 1873 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Series IV. G. Lauriston Walsh Files, President of Alpha Delta Phi Alumni Association
  - ACEF Mission Statement (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - ACEF News Articles, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - ACEF Outstanding Loans, 1973-1987 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - ACEF: Olson, Eric, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - ACEF Plates/Dining Room, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - ACEF Pledges, Class of '86, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - ACEF pledges and cont., 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - ACEF pledges delinquent, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Pledge Forms (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - ACEF pledge loan, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Pledges, 1986-1987 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ACEF pledge: Ritchey, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - ACEF Pledges spreadsheet, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - ACEF prizes and trophies, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - ACEF John Rice literary awards, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Rueby process for plaques, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - ACEF reports, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - ACEF Samuel Ells Purchase, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - ACEF Secretary's minutes, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Shaw, William: Attorney at Law, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - ACEF: Sinclair, Leroy, 1985-1988 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - ACEF: Sonne, David, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - ACEF speakers program (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - ACEF Stewart-Howe, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - ACEF transmittals, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - ACEF Bruce Hart (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - ACEF Midjo, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
  - ACEF IRS, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Douglas Jimerson, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - ACEF Lennox, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - ACEF Loan Apps, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Phil Lyon (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Prof. Marchem, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - ACEF transmittals, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - ACEF Members, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - ACEF: Meskunas Ford, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - New York Dinner, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - San Francisco Dinner, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - ACEF Washington Dinner, 1987-1989 (Box 16, Folder 41-43)
  - ACEF Dyson Pledge, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Ellis, Thomas, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Engle, Robert, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - ACEF expenses, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - ACEF financial, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - ACEF fall, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - ACEF student loan application letter (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Floor plan, 777 Stewart Ave. (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Tom Foulkes, 1986-1988 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - ACEF Foulkes correspondence and trustee meetings (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Tom Foulkes will addition, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - ACEF Freshman literary prize, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Grants and awards, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Memorandums, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - ACEF, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - ACEF Board Meeting, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - ACEF Board members (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Booth Obituaries, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - ACEF Thomas Bower, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - David Brooke, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Brothers, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - ACEF charitable life, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Boston Dinner, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - ACEF California dinner, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - ACEF June dinner, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - ACEF Lenox dinner (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - ACEF NYC dinner, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - NY Dinner, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - ADP Newsletter, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Noise control (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Oldies but Goodies (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - ADP International, Bruce Olson, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - ADP Parents memo, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Active chapter phone list (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - ADP petty cash (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Resumes (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Pledge class collectives, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Pledge examination (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Pledge manuals (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - ADP presidents (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Proxy (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Centennial publication, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Randolph and Carpenter, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - ADP Gilber F. Rankin, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - ADP Cornell literary contest winners, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Literary (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - ADP Cornell Lovitt, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Maintenance (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Mike Mallett, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Mayans, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - ADP Ian McMillan (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - ACEF laws (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - ADP building inspection, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bylaws (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - ACEF political forum, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Alumni weekend, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Columbia press releases, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - ACEF members list, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - ACEF IRS, 1962 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - ACEF 2nd Mortgage (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - AIFC (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - ACEF Annual financial statements (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Ted Booth obituary, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - John Brook, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - ACEF Correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 17, Folder 26-28)
  - Cornell Charter, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - ADP Inc., 1989 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - ADPhi AIFC, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - ADPhi Expenses (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Alumni convention report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - ADP Cornell pledge manual (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Chapter advisor, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - ADPhi Alumni correspondence, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Cornell in Crisis (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Policies, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Cornell Class, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - ADP Correspondence, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - ADP Cornell alumni presidents, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Davis-Ulmer Sprinkler Co, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Desilva, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Alpha Delt, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Accounts received, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Activities monthly statements (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Active chapter, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 47-50)
  - ADP Cornell annual meeting, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Bod update, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - ADP Biographical forms, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Current brothers, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Board meeting, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Bender, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Brady, James (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Brooke, 1986-1987 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Balfour, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Budget, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Cert Corp (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Clothing (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - ADPhi, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Expenses, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - ADP Active chapter presidents (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - ADPhi purchase, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Accounts payable (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Accounts received, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - ADP Cornell active chapter, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 69-70)
  - Annual report, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Sciar Abba Walker, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Alcohol (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Alumni, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Alumni profiles (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Alumni weekend (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Annual givings, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - Director's memo, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Meeting payoff contest, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 2-4)
  - Fire Cornell (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Flags (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Corporation financial statements, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - ADP furniture inventory (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Fraternity statistics, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Directors meeting corp, 1981-1985 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - ADP minutes, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - ADP cornell event registration procedures, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - ADP Permanent financial records, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Financial receipts transmittals, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Fire Engines, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Alumni corp fiscal report, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Fraternal laws, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Fraternity statistics, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Greek- Columns (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - ADP G10 Lenox, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - GLW annual, 1987-1989 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Hample, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Hazing Regulations (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Historic Landmark designation, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Homecoming, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 25-26)
  - ADP Honor Roll of Donors, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Housing contract, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - House Improvements (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - ADP Housing, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Housing Inspection, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - ADP Cornell Housing Survey (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Homecoming weekend, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Income tax, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Important dates (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Change in account, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Initiation, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Insurance Liability, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - IRS, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Kitchen, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Legacies (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Life safety inspector reports (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Literary contest, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Mortgage payoffs (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Montreal Convention, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Treasurer's report, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - ACEF Transmittals, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Treasurer's report, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - ACEF Trustee meeting (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - ACEF Will addition (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Mike Zak, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Real Estate Council, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - ADP financials, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Receipts, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Registration frat-sorority (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Rice, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Housing contract (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Reunion Weekend, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Reunion Weekend, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Frank T. Rhodes, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Rush, 1986-1988 (Box 19, Folder 3-4)
  - SMC, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 5-6)
  - Student Management, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Stewart 777 active officers, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Manuals (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Stewart 777 maintenance and repair (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Stewart 777 mortgage, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Stewart 777 plot plan, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Stewart 777 property taxes, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Stewart 777 active rentals (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Stewart Howe, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Stewart mailing list, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - SMC active chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - SMC, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - ADP Smoke alarm system, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - SMC Kitchen, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - SMC, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - ADP Cornell songs (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - SMC alumni account, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - SMC Active chapter balance sheets, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - SMC Corp. profile and costs, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Summer maintenance, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Sword and Spear ADP active chapter (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - James Totman, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - 3D Printers, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Transmittals, 1987-1989 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Tax info, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Ties and certificates, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Undergraduate president's report (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - John Varoli- famous, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Victory club (Box 19, Folder 35-36)
  - Wigginton resume, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Harold T Wright, 1987 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - ADP Cornell active chapter, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Eugene Wolfe, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 40)
- Series V. Photographs and negatives
  - Group portraits and 2 unidentified negatives, 1872-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1-54)
  - Group and composite photographs, fraternity house and house fire, campus buildings including Rice Hall, Teagle Hall and Observatory, 1967-2000 (Box 4)
  - Group photographs and fraternity house, 1926, 1939 (Box 5)
  - Photograph album, including road renovations, Howie Schaffer, group and misc., ca.1880's, 1900's, 2001 (Box 6)
  - Photographs, 1923-2003 (Box 7)
  - Group photo, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Unidentified portraits, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 2-8)
  - Individual portraits, 1900-1907 (Box 8, Folder 9-27)
  - Group photograph, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Group photograph, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Empty photo album - photos removed and placed in Box 8 (Box 9)
  - Alpha Delta Phi Photo Album, assembled by William P. Abbott, 1875-1880 (Box 10)
    Contains photos of faculty during the time, including Ezra Cornell, A. D. White, Willard Fiske, Goldwin Smith; Cornell crew team of 1875 and Taughannock Falls prior to rock fall
  - Alpha Delta Phi Photo Album, assembled by Richard H. Cobb, ca. 1905-1910 (Box 11)
    Contains photos of fraternity house including interior shots and the fire that destroyed the Chi Psi house, the “goat house”, other miscellaneous photos candid/group shots and canon fire on campus
  - Photos of initiation weekend 2004 and misc., ca. 1970's-1990's, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Portrait album of members, ca. 1883 (Box 13)
  - Photos of fraternity house and misc., ca. 1800’s-1900’s (Box 14)
  - Photos of Charles Kendall Adams (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Group portraits, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 4-9)
  - Group portraits, 1872-1881 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Series VI. Other
  - Alpha Delta Phi embosser, MU-2046 (Box 2)
  - Sketches of fraternity house, 1980 (Box 5)
  - The Face behind the Mask, by John Minahan, 1986 (Box 12)
  - 2 CDs containing 2 photos of paintings by Louis Agassiz Fuertes: “Owl” (CD-1960) and “March” (CD-1961) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Song books and CD of songs (CD-1962), 1888-1994 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Decals and 1940’s book plates (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Alpha Delta Phi at Cornell, Inc., 1972, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Dinner for James E. Rice, Jr. and his 1926 certificate of membership, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Song book, n.d. (Box 13)
  - Annual initiation program, 1926 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Reunion invitation, 1876 (Box 15, Folder 2)